IRENE WU

WEB DEVELOPER & UX/UI DESIGNER

DETAILS

irenewu222@gmail.com 778-859-9204

SKILLS

Front-end Coding Web Development UX/UI Design Responsive Design User Testing

HTML, CSS
Sass
Javascript, jQuery
Next.js, React.js
RESTful API
Github, Git
Figma
Photoshop
Illustrator

Communication
Collaboration
Organization
Time Management
Problem Solving

LANGUAGES

English Mandarin Taiwanese

HIGHLIGHTS

Front-end developer with 2 years experience in closely collaborating with teams in designing and developing interactive and responsive cross platform web applications. Competent in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, as well as using React.js and Next.js. Eager to learn new things and use my skills to create quality web applications.

EDUCATION

DIGITAL DESIGN & DEVELOPMENT

BRITISH COLUMBIA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY, SEPTEMBER 2020 - MAY 2022 Designed and developed interactive and responsive cross-platform web applications using best practices.

VISUAL ARTS MAJOR

LANGLEY FINE ARTS SECONDARY, SEPTEMBER 2015 - JUNE 2020 Learned various art skills, including photoshooting and designing, as well as using Adobe Creative Cloud products.

EXPERIENCE

Kalm (Mental Health Web Application)

FRONT-END DEVELOPER, UX/UI DESIGNER, SEPTEMBER 2021 - DEC 2021

- Designed and developed a user-friendly, responsive web app.
- Created reusable UI components using React and Styled-components.
- Organized and managed all files for easy accessibility.
- Communicated closely with full-stack developers about the design and front-end.

reVamp (Sustainability Web Application)

LEAD FRONT-END DEVELOPER, UX/UI DESIGNER, JANUARY 2021 - MAY 2021

- Conducted throrough user testing to create a user friendly application.
- Polished the front-end to ensure all functionalities are working.
- Helped others when they are facing difficulty in the coding process.
- Developed strong time management through collaboration, in a tight schedule.